proofhub.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy | ProofHub

The privacy of your data is important to us.

We log all access to all accounts by IP address, so we can always verify that no unauthorized access has happened for as long as the logs are kept. Only in case you ask us to, we’ll access your account to help you with a problem or to fix of a software bug.

This policy applies to data that is collected, used, and retained by us in the United States.

### Identity & access

We ask for your name, company name, phone and email address when you signup for ProofHub. This is done to setup and personalize your new account and send you invoices, updates, or other important information. The phone number you provide is used only when you ask to be called for assistance, help setting up the account. Your personal information will never be sold to third parties, and we won’t use your name or company in marketing statements without your permission.

When you contact ProofHub with a question or to ask for help, we keep the email address and correspondence for future reference. When you browse our marketing pages, we’ll track them for statistical purposes (like tracking the sources of signups, market research, conversion rates and to test new designs) and to improve the content of our web pages and the quality of our service.

You always have the right to access the personal information we store about you. And, if you wish to further limit our use of your personal information, please contact Alex Hood at [privacyshield@proofhub.com](mailto:privacyshield@proofhub.com).

Users of ProofHub can store any type of information in ProofHub, but ProofHub does not access or share that data, and does not know what type of data you or other users are storing. The data is only used by the account owner and invited users as they intend to use it.

The only times we’ll ever share your info is to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, group, place, region, nation,etc., violations of our Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.

### Law enforcement

While we may be required to disclose your personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements, ProofHub won’t hand your data over to law enforcement unless a court order says we have to. We flat-out reject requests from local and federal law enforcement when they seek data without a court order. And unless we’re legally prevented from it, we’ll always inform you when such requests are made.

### Encryption

All data is encrypted via SSL/TLS when transmitted from our servers to your browser. The database backups are also encrypted. The data isn’t encrypted while it’s live in our database (since it needs to be ready to send to you when you need it), but we have checks in place to secure your data at rest. You can read more about it on our security page.

### Cookies

In order to improve our services and the website, and provide more convenient, relevant experiences to you, we and our vendors may use “cookies”, “web beacons”, and similar devices to track your activities.

### Third Parties and data storage

ProofHub uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run ProofHub. The current list of vendors is available upon request.

Although ProofHub owns the code, databases, and all rights to the ProofHub application, you retain all rights to your data.

### Deleted data

When you cancel your account, we’ll ensure that nothing is stored on our servers past 15 days. Anything you delete on your account while it’s active will also be purged within 15 days (deleted data stays in the trash can for 15 days, unless the trash can is emptied manually and data gets purged immediately).

### EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework

ProofHub complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>.

### EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Complaints

In compliance with the US-EU and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles, ProofHub commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Alex Hood at ProofHub at [privacyshield@ProofHub.com](mailto:privacyshield@ProofHub.com), or by mail at ProofHub, LLC, 340 S Lemon Ave #8090. Walnut, CA 91789, USA.

### Changes and questions

ProofHub may periodically update this policy. We'll notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your ProofHub primary holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

If you'd like to access, change, delete your personal information or have any questions about this privacy policy, contact Alex Hood at ProofHub at [privacyshield@ProofHub.com](mailto:privacyshield@ProofHub.com).
